My father was an innocent man, destroyed by powerful people
我父亲本是无辜人 却被权贵陷害
The Graysons are behind this
Grayson家族是幕后黑手
They're gonna pay
他们将血债血偿
I've dedicated my life to avenging his death
我将不惜生命为他复仇
Eventually,someone's gonna find you out
最后 总会有人揭穿你
And I won't stop until they've all paid the price
我不会停下 直到所有人都付出代价
You will always be the clueless frat boy who crashed your car,
你永远是那个混在兄弟会的小屁孩 撞烂了自己的车
crushed my spine,and never looked back
撞坏了我的脊椎 不会去承担后果
She lost her job
她工作丢了
Helping her get another was the least I could do
帮她再找一份工作是我唯一能做的
I thought you were set for life,Sara.I'm sorry
Sara 我以为你会得到很好的照顾 我很抱歉
Why are you doing this,Daniel
Daniel 你为什么要这样做呢
To earn your forgiveness
来获得你的原谅
You're the first person in a long time to be able to make me smile
这么长时间以来 你是唯一一个能让我笑的人
Jack went to Conrad and told him that Patrick tampered with his brakes
Jack告诉Conrad 是Patrick在他的刹车上动了手脚
He's probably being chased out of town as we speak
在我们说话这个时候 他估计已经被赶走了
Conrad is a ruthless man.You're not safe
Conrad是个很残忍的人 你在这不安全
- I can't. - Go.
- 我不能 - 快走
Growing up,my father said the ocean was a great escape
小时候 我爸爸说 大海是最好的避难所
As time passed,I also learned that its expanse holds greater secrets
慢慢长大 我觉得宽广的大海 能容下好多秘密
and the ability to hold mine...
包括我的
And that like love,it is at its heart fluid,powerful,and sometimes violent
就像爱一样 藏在血液里面 那么的强烈 有时甚至是粗暴的
Next time you're here, the authorities will have Victoria in custody
下次你来这里的时候 警察局已经把Victotia关起来了
Soon after,I'll take you away from everything
很快 我就会把你带走 远离这一切
And everyone
远离所有人
But in its harshest reality, the ocean is a barrier
但最难过的是 大海也是一道栏杆
separating you from those you love
隔开你和你爱的人
When this is done,I'll never see my sister again... Or Nolan
等这一切都结束 我就再也不能见到 我妹妹和Nolan了
I know
我知道
You'll be okay
你会没事的
Are you writing a letter to Patrick-- Your natural born killer
你在给Patrick 那个天生的杀手写信吗
It's the only means of correspondence
这是唯一的联络方式
I have to keep away from the prying eyes of the minions
我可要小心提防那些狗腿的眼睛
I'm sure you have looking for him
我知道肯定你在找他
Why would I waste the time and effort
我为什么要浪费这个时间跟精力呢
It's that smug smirk I'm going to miss the least
在我们分好财产 从此不相往来以后
after we've converted our money, and I have left you for good
我绝不会想念你这副 小人得志的嘴脸
Now there's an action that may compel me to hire some folks to go looking for your boy
这个行为可能会逼我派人 去找回你那个儿子
Excuse my confusion,Conrad,
是我搞错了吗 Conrad
but are you threatening Patrick to keep me by your side
你在用Patrick威胁我 让我留在你身边
You know,I believe I am...
我想是的
Starting with your magnificent presence downstairs for the little Grayson confab
从你擅长的华丽出场开始吧 到楼下的家庭会议去
you've obviously forgotten about
你显然忘了这事
I've enlisted a PR
我请了一个公关专家
specialist to help right the course of my trajectory
来帮我回到正轨上
So if you value Patrick's freedom, you know,
所以如果你重视Patrick的自由
you may want to find some public worth in the family you still have
还是为仍在你身边的家人 做些贡献吧
I still don't see why we're here
我还是不懂我们在这里干嘛
If my father wants to rehab his image, he can do it himself
我爸爸要重塑名声 他自己来就可以了
I've already educated him on re-branding
我已经告诉他什么是形象重塑了
and how you're all an extension of his good name
其中包括你们也是他形象的一部分
I'm a Clarke
我姓Clarke
Whoever you are
不管你姓什么
That whole "slumming it in Montauk" thing... Gold
在蒙托克体验生活这个点很好
People love it when the rich help the poor
人们就是喜欢看有钱人帮助穷人
But where's the bang for my wedding buck
但婚礼的声势呢
There were no cameras when you went ring shopping
你们买结婚戒指的时候没有拍照
Has the venue even been announced
婚礼场地宣布了没有
Who's making the cake
结婚蛋糕出自谁的手
We are not a very showy couple
我们不是那种爱出风头的情侣
Is it we?Or is it you?
我们? 还是只是你而已?
I am damn good at doing my research, and you're a mystery
我很擅长做资料搜集 但你就是一个神秘人
You need to be more like Daniel
你应该像Daniel那样
That publisher's profile is exactly the kind of rebound story I love
出版人资料上的重生故事 正正就是我最喜欢看到的
Hurt a girl... Tortured soul... Redemption
伤害了一个女孩 被折磨的灵魂 赎罪
And I just hired Sara at the Stowaway
我给Sara在偷渡者酒吧找了份工作
- Really? - We ran into her. It's a long story
- 是吗 - 我们刚好碰到她 说来话长
One I need to hear
我就是想要这种故事
If I am to guide your father back into America's hearts,
如果我要把你们爸爸带回到 美国人民的心中
I run the narrative on this family from here on out
这个家的故事以后由我来讲
I see you couldn't even extend the courtesy of waiting, - Ms Preston
连等待的礼节都免了啊 Preston小姐
- "Bizzy," please. - Bizzy
- 请叫我Bizzy - Bizzy
It's such a pleasure,Victoria
Victoria 见到你太荣幸了
And I figured I might as well get a jump on the kids so as not to waste your time
我觉得我先跟孩子们打好招呼 免得浪费你的时间
While I applaud your gumption,Bizzy,
Bizzy 尽管我赞赏你的干劲
I feel this Independence Day party I'm throwing,
我觉得我举办的独立日派对
along with Emily's wedding shower,
还有Emily的结婚送礼会
should prove sufficient for the society papers
已经给媒体提供了充足的素材
That won't help if those rags think that you two are still at odds
如果那些人还是觉得你们不合 那么这些都是没用的
The last event you attended led to a fight worthy of pay-per-view
上次你们一起出席活动时的争吵 都够格上电视台的收费节目了
And since there is little benefit in positioning Conrad
但让Conrad扮演危机家庭中的 大家长角色
as master of a house divided,
还是有那么一点好处的
I need to rewrite your story... Pronto
我需要尽管改写这个故事
And how do you propose to do that
那你觉得应该怎么做呢
First off,I am plugging your 4th of July party
首先 在7月4号的派对上
as the reintroduction of the happy Grayson clan,
我将重新向大家介绍 快乐的Grayson一家
followed by a mother/daughter-in-law goodwill tour
然后我会帮你们安排
that I will lay out for you
一个婆媳愉快的旅程
when the three of us have lunch tomorrow
详情我们三个明天午饭再谈
Right there... That's all I need-- You two
我需要的 就是你们两个
And that's what I'm gonna get
我也一定会成功的
Trying to get some scoop on the wedding
想了解一些婚礼的独家新闻?
They've got big things planned
他们策划的很隆重
I'm sure they do
我猜也是
What brings you by
你怎么来了
I... brought you some macaroons to welcome you back
我带了些马卡龙 欢迎你回来
Thanks. That's a nice surprise
谢谢 真好
How was LA
洛杉矶之旅还好吗
Wining and dining photographers for Voulez is not as glamorous as one might think
为了Voulez跟摄影师们吃饭喝酒 不是想象中那么光鲜好玩的
Oh,really?Weird
是吗 那可真奇怪
I've had a totally different experience when doing it
我去的时候感觉完全不一样
I don't suppose you're free tonight
我想你今晚是没空了
He comes bearing gifts, and now he's looking for a date
他带着礼物来 现在想来个约会
I should leave town more often
我应该多出差
But no
但是不行
I have too much work to catch up on with the wedding approaching
婚礼逼近 我还有很多工作要赶
Ah,it'll still be here tomorrow
工作可以明天再说
Don't let the Graysons take over your life
不要让Grayson一家占据你的生活
- Hi. - I've lost my touch
- 嗨 - 我水平下降了
A week later,and all I've dug up is a one-way flight from Philly to Richmond
一周过去 我只找到了一张从 Philly到Richmond的单程飞机
I just want to know that Patrick's all right
我只想确定Patrick没事
Well,you should be happy that he's not here
那你该庆幸他不在这儿
He would also be scrutinized by the publicist Conrad hired
不然他也会被Conrad聘请的公共 折磨一番
She wants me and Victoria to play nice for the press
她想让我和Victoria在媒体面前 和平相处
Oh,you and Vicki,besties--
你和Vicki 好朋友
That kind of runs counter to your master plan of framing her for your murder now
那就和诬陷她谋杀你的计划 背道而驰了
Exactly.Which is why PR maven Bizzy Preston is becoming a problem
对 所以这个公共专家 Bizzy Preston是个问题
that I don't have time for
可我没时间处理她
What,you know her
怎么 你认识她
And loathe her
还憎恶她
Back in the day,I was,uh,dating this guy
那时我在和一个男的约会
It was casual... fun
只是寻欢作乐
Then I met his sister-- Up-and-coming pop star,Sage
然后我遇到了他妹妹 流行音乐新星 Sage
And she was more casual,more fun... And as it turned out,married
她更加随性有趣 可结果她已经结婚了
The press got ahold of our one-hit wonder, and Bizzy squashed it...
媒体抓到了我们昙花一现的恋情 Bizzy把它压下去了
By claiming I was gay
声称我是同志
I remember when that happened.It was right when we met
我记得 那时候我们刚刚认识
I didn't know that she was behind it
我不知道她在背后操纵一切
Neither did my father
我父亲也不知道
After years of being estranged,
我们已经疏远了好些年
Nolcorp's success had finally gotten us back on good terms,
Nolcorp的成功终于 让我们的关系好了起来
even planning a visit to New York to see my R&D facility
他甚至计划来纽约看的我研发设施
Programmed a robot to open him a beer
我给机器人编好程 会给他开啤酒
Then... He read the press release, canceled his trip... Never spoke to me again
然后他看了新闻 取消了行程 再也没和我说过话
I'm sorry,Nolan
抱歉 Nolan
Bizzy's the one who should be sorry
Bizzy才是要抱歉的那个
And we have to stop you from becoming the next victim of her PR machine
我们要阻止你成为她公关机器的 下一个受害者
She makes a living covering her clients' secrets
她以掩饰客户的秘密为生
We just have to expose them
我们只要让秘密曝光就好
Yeah,but that's not a simple task
对 但是任务不简单
She would do anything to protect 'em, and the greater the retainer,
她会不惜一切保护他们
the bigger her allegiance
付钱越多 她就越忠心
And I know a family who's paying top dollar
我知道那家付了大价钱
What are you thinking
你在想什么
She could help us with Victoria before we make her suffer
在我们折磨她之前 在Victoria的事上她可以协助我们
It's not that easy
没那么简单
She's smart,dangerous,lethal with information
她聪明 危险 善于扭曲信息
Well,I'm not afraid to give her some
那我不怕再给她一点料
It's time she found out about my first husband
是时候让她发现我的第一任老公了
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-Proudly Presents
-=伊甸园美剧  http://bbs.sfile2012.com=- -=伊甸园字幕站   http://ytet.org=- 荣誉出品 本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com/bbs=-Sync: YTET- 可可与可心
-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组=- 翻译:becausel 可可 豆芽小鱼 藉秋风 小V 校对:Music4d 时间轴:YTET-可可与可心
Revenge Season3Episode 7
复仇 第三季 第七集
Things were slow back there,so,I whipped up a little something
现在生意不多 所以我做了一些小东西
Is this another attempt to get desserts put on the menu
还想尝试把甜点写进菜单吗
Can you blame a girl for trying
我想试试 你会责怪吗
I'm glad you joined the crew around here
我很高兴你能加入我们
You're a-- You're a breath of fresh air
你带来了新鲜空气
Thanks
谢谢
I got some stuff to do in the storeroom
我要去库房做些事
I was just on my way out to lunch
我正要出门吃午饭
I hope you don't mind me stopping by
顺道过来 希望你不介意
Well,it is a bar
这是个酒吧
That's kinda the point,right
这很正常不是么
You settling in
你习惯了吗
It's only been a week,but I can't complain
只待了一周 不过没什么可抱怨的
You obviously miss your job at the bakery
你明显很想念面包房的工作
I know that look
我了解这表情
It means you got something on the brain
你脑子里在谋划什么
I know this pastry thing has always been a dream of yours
我知道做糕点一直是你的梦想
And this might sound crazy,but...
听起来或许不可思议 不过
What if you were to make the cake for my wedding
我的婚礼蛋糕请你做怎么样
Right... 'Cause that wouldn't be weird
对 因为那不会很奇怪
Only if we make it weird.Come on.We haven't hired anybody yet
我们不觉得奇怪就好 拜托 我们还没有请到人
You know... When I saw you the other night after my shift,
那晚下班后看到你
I thought you were just handing me a bunch of crap
我以为你说要获取我的原谅
about earning my forgiveness
不过是一通废话
I told you,that's not who I am anymore
我说过 我已经变了
- I want to help. - I don't want your charity,Danny
- 我想要帮忙 - 我不需要你的施舍 Danny
Good,'cause I'm not offering you any
很好 我也没有这个意思
What I am offering is a chance at a job you want--
我只是给你一个机会 做你喜欢的工作
One that could be good for you
一个对你有益的工作
Think about it
考虑一下
Like I said,he'd be perfect for a profile piece in your magazine
正如我说 他非常适合上你杂志的简介板块
Think about it
考虑考虑
Sorry
对不起
This thing beats more often than my heart
这东西响的比我心跳还频繁
Especially now that I'm keeping you all dry under my umbrella
尤其现在我要保护你们
Conrad did not tell me just how much this family was weighing him down
Conrad没有告诉我 这个家有多拖累他
I don't understand.Is that why I'm here
我不懂 这是你找我的原因吗
a blogger called about a piece that I planted about you and Daniel--
有个博客写手找到了我 我安排了一篇你和Daniel的文章
How socialite Emily Thorne waited to find her Prince Charming
名媛Emily Thorne如何耐心等待 她的白马王子
It's... good
不错的
But... This weasel claims to have proof that you were hitched before
但是 这只黄鼠狼声称有证据 表明你以前结过婚
What
什么
I was really young.It was a mistake
我当时太年轻 那就是个错误
I mean,surely you understand
我相信你能理解
Actually... I'm one of the lucky few who was right about her high school sweetheart
事实上 我是少数的幸运人之一 在高中就找到自己的归属
Jeff and I have been together for 22 years
Jeff和我在一起22年了
And we are still as in love as I'm sure you and Daniel are
我们还是很相爱 我想你和Daniel也是
This can't get out
这不能透露出去
I'm a gravedigger,babe
我是掘墓专家 亲爱的
I bury things bigger than this every day
我埋下的丑闻比这轰动多了
Good,'cause nobody can know,especially Victoria
那就好 不能让任何人知道 尤其是Victoria
We're not really the best of friends
我们关系不怎么样
I just can't win with her
我就是不招她待见
If she finds this out,she will never forgive me
如果被她发现了 永远都不会原谅我
Well... I caught the bullet this time
这次是被我挡下了
But secrets have a way of bleeding out
但纸包不住火
So let's cut to the chase
我就开门见山了
What else are you hiding
你还有什么秘密
Nothing,I swear
没有了 我发誓
Can I help you with something
有什么需要帮忙的
Conrad's hired a publicist who's determined to put a sheen on everything we do,
Conrad雇了个公关人员 想要给我们家每件事都镀上光环
including promoting this wedding,
包括宣传这场婚礼
which if we don't act quickly, it'll be too late to do anything
如果我们不快点下手 可能就来不及了
I thought you were relying on Jack Porter - to break them up
我以为你寄希望于Jack Porter 来拆散他们呢
- I've heard that he's courting Ms Lemarchal
我听说他已经在追求Lemarchal小姐了
So clearly that won't be coming to fruition
所以这个方案实现不了了
- Then we'll find another way. - Oh,we won't
- 那我们就另谋出路 - 不是我们
You will
是你来
My son has no shortage of hatred towards you
我儿子反正也看你不顺眼
So get back in Emily's life... And more importantly,her bed
你就顺势回到Emily的生活中去 重点是 回到她的床上去
The blogger persona was convincing
博客写手这事她买账了
Let's just hope Bizzy spreads the news like I want her to
希望Bizzy能如我所愿 把消息放出去
Oh,trust me
相信我
She knows that sharing information like that keeps her on the Grayson payroll
她清楚分享这种情报 能让她在Grayson家赚到更多
And once she does,the two of us will Biz-mantle her with glee
她一旦告密 我们就能欢快地把她解决了
You sure you're up for it,Grandpa
你确定你要参与进来吗 老爷爷
I'm not getting older,just... wiser
我没有变老 只是更成熟了而已
But trying to unearth Bizzy's clients' secrets is taking longer than I thought
但是想挖出Bizzy客户的秘密 比我想象的要难
Hacking her proton 5 firewall will take time that I don't have
我没那么多时间 破解她的五重防火墙
Why the look
这什么表情
If this had happened a few years ago,
如果这发生在五年前
you would have thrown a martini in her face and called it a day
你早就把马提尼克泼她脸上 撒手不管了
But now... I'm standing up for myself
- 但现在 - 我要为自己而战
I just... Buried the pain of what happened with my father,
我把 和父亲的不愉快收了起来
but because of you,I'm not just facing it
因为你 我不仅能够从容面对
I'm doing something
还能对此有所作为
I've learned a lot from you,Ems
我从你那里学到好多 Ems
We made a great team
我们是好搭档
Well,if we're gonna win... We're gonna need a new game plan
如果我们想赢 就需要新的计划
I don't have the time for this firewall, so we've got to get her password
我没时间搞这些防火墙了 我们要搞到她的密码
Except that phone never leaves her hands
可她手机从不离手
Maybe it doesn't need to
也许不用离手
I'm glad I decided to take the evening off
很高兴我决定今晚放假
It's beautiful out here,isn't it
这里很美 不是吗
Yeah,it's like your own little sanctuary
是啊 这就像是你的小小避难所
Where no one can find us
在这没人能找到我们
- What.Have I done something wrong? - No.No
- 怎么了 我做错什么了 - 不 没有 只是
It's... Let's just try to enjoy the movie and have another glass of wine
我们还是好好看电影 喝葡萄酒吧
Unless... I can go downstairs and make another drink
或者 我下楼调点别的
No,I don't need anything from the bar
不用了 酒吧里没有我想要的
Wine it is,then
那接着喝这个吧
That's not what I meant
我不是这个意思
Okay,I think it's best if I go
好吧 我想我该走了
- Margaux. - It's okay.I have an early morning
- Margaux - 没关系 我明天要早起开会
Enjoy your beautiful evening
好好享受这美好的夜晚吧
You're late
你来晚了
Daniel held me up
Daniel拖延了时间
He wants his ex-girlfriend to make our wedding cake
他想让他前女友 来给我们做婚礼蛋糕
He set up a tasting at my house tomorrow
他明天要在我家搞个试吃会
Do you suspect something's amiss
你怀疑里面有诈
No.I'm sure he's doing it out of guilt
没有 他一定是因为内疚才这么做
Daniel's the reason I needed to meet with you
Daniel是我来见你的原因
Victoria's compelled me to get back into your orbit
Victoria逼我回到你身边
in order to drive a wedge between the two of you
以此来破坏你们的关系
Well,that's not an option,not this close to the wedding
坚决不行 尤其是婚礼将至
Yeah,but if I don't see it through, I may lose access to the Graysons
没错 可如果我不照做 我就无法自由出入Grayson家了
Maybe there's a third way
也许还有第三种方案
And that is
你意思是
To be seen together...
让别人看到我们在一起 但是以我们的方式
This is the last one,I promise
我保证 这是最后一款了
Are you kidding me?Each one's been better than the last
开什么玩笑 每个都要比前一个更好吃
Are these family recipes
这是家传的食谱吗
Yeah,passed down from my mom's side
没错 从我妈妈这边传下来的
Well,your mom taught you well
噢 名师出高徒哇
Well,she raised me and my brother after my dad ditched us,
在我爸抛弃我们后 她自己把我和弟弟养大
so everything I know I learned from her,including how to make a mess
所以我都是从她那学的 包括怎么把这搞得一团糟
I am so sorry about this disaster
很抱歉把这里弄成这样
Oh,don't worry about it
别担心
But... I better stop,or I'll be full for my lunch with Victoria
不过 我不能再吃了 不然没法跟Victoria一起吃午饭了
Well,if it'd help make the lunch shorter, I'd say eat up
为了缩短午饭时间 我建议你多吃点
Thanks again... For giving me a shot
再次感谢你 给我这个机会
Of course.Thank you .See ya
举手之劳 谢谢 回见
Hey... I really appreciate you considering this
嘿 很感谢你能接受
It's just something I... I want to do,you know
我就是想 做点什么 你知道
It's a great thing that you're doing
你做的事情很有意义
And I... I think she'll make a wonderful wedding cake
而且我觉得她会做出超棒的婚礼蛋糕
Me,too
我也觉得
I'll see you later,okay
稍后见 好吗
- You got the job. - Shut up
- 你被录取啦 - 别逗我了
- Seriously? - I'm serious
- 你说真的? - 真的
Man,she is way more mature than I am
哥们 她比我成熟多了
I mean... Letting your fiancé's ex make your wedding cake--
让未婚夫的前女友做婚礼蛋糕
If the tables were turned,
要是换做我
I would be so jealous and would have canceled the whole thing
我肯定会吃醋到把婚礼都取消掉
Oh,well,that's Emily
Emily为人就是这样
And you... Even asking her to let me make the cake-- That took guts
还有你 竟然敢向她提出来 胆子真大
I mean,what if these were awful
万一我做得很烂呢
I knew they wouldn't be
我知道不会的
I gotta say that,uh... Forgiveness thing you were looking for...
我必须要说 你在寻求我原谅的道路上
This goes a long way toward it
已经走了一大步
-  Well...I should clean up. - Okay
- 好了 我要把这里打扫干净了 - 好的
Hey,let me help you .I got it
我来帮你 我来吧
- I can help - No,Danny,you hired me.It's my job
- 我可以帮忙 - 不 Danny 你雇了我 这是我的工作
Then I'm giving you the rest of the day off
那现在你可以下班了
Go home
回家吧
So... How was your date with Margaux
你和Margaux的约会怎么样
Things were fine... Until... they weren't
一切都挺好的 然后 就不好了
- Okay.What happened . - I don't know
- 好吧 怎么了 - 我不知道
She just-- She left in the middle of it
她中途就走了
What,for no reason.What's up,Jack
怎么 无缘无故就走了 发生什么了 Jack
I just... I blew it
是我 我搞砸了
I mean,I didn't want to,but I just-- I couldn't handle it
我也不想 可是我 我做不来
You know what this is,right
你知道是怎么回事 是吗
- Yeah. - I think... Maybe it's time to face it
- 是 - 我想 是时候面对这一切了
I must admit,I was a bit surprised when I heard from your publicist
我得承认 你的公关找给我时 我有点震惊
So she tells me you're looking for some press coverage
她说你想要些新闻版面
Oh,uh,there must be some confusion
这里面一定是有误会
What Ms Preston offered you was an exclusive
Preston小姐提供的是独家新闻
Conrad Grayson is back
Conrad Grayson正式回归
He's a survivor... A laudatory profile of sorts
他是个幸存者 来个满篇的溢美之词
It's out of the question
这不可能
We have to maintain journalistic integrity
我们必须有新闻准则
And covering Daniel's wedding isn't a conflict of interest
报道Daniel的婚礼就没有问题吗
Touché,Mr Grayson
说得好 Grayson先生
But there is a difference between a society piece
不过 社会新闻和帮你打广告
and an advertisement for you
还是有区别的
Now,if you were to give me access to all your papers and... archives...
但如果 你所有的文件和档案 都能供我查阅
Then maybe we could talk
也许还有的谈
Ms Lemarchal,I'm not here to dwell on the past
Lemarchal小姐 我不是来耽溺往事的
Well,if you're not willing to be totally honest with me,
如果你不能对我毫无保留
I'm not comfortable moving forward
我觉得没必要继续
But I'm sure there's a story in you no one expects
但我确信 你一定有让人始料未及的故事
You just need the guts to tell it
你只需勇敢地把它讲出来
You see how easy this is
你们看 多简单
With you two on the same page,
你们俩和谐共处 不抢镜头
it won't pull focus as we can ease Conrad back into the spotlight
我就能把Conrad重新推到聚光灯下
Well,this itinerary is too aggressive
这个行程太紧凑了
Surely the 200 people I'm hosting this evening means I've done my duty
我今晚要招待两百个人 应该算完成我的任务了
You know better than most that changing public opinion takes time
你比谁都清楚 扭转大众观念需要时间
And I have mere weeks until everyone sees you
距新娘送礼会没有几周的时间了
as the new ideal of a mother and daughter-in-law - at the bridal shower
到时 我要让所有人看到你们成为 良好婆媳关系的典范
That should be an interesting challenge
真是个有意思的挑战呢
Not for women of your stature
以你们的地位 这不算挑战
If your conflict creates such sparks, imagine what a partnership can do
如果冲突就能碰撞出这么多火花 想象一下你们将是多好的搭档
Well,I'd certainly marvel to see it
我非常期望看到
Aiden,what a coincidence
Aiden 这么巧
Well,in-- In truth,it's not
实际上 不是巧合
I know I'm-- I'm being forward, but I was hoping to steal Ms Thorne
我知道这太直接了 但我想和Thorne小姐单独待会儿
I have nothing to say to you
我和你没什么好说的
Why don't you go,Emily
你还是去吧 Emily
You clearly have things to resolve
看来你们还有事要处理
Thank you for lunch,Bizzy
谢谢你的午餐 Bizzy
- Of course. - After you.Thank you
- 客气 - 你先请 谢谢
Sweet girl
真是个好姑娘
Emily obviously craves your approval
Emily显然渴求你的认同
You know,I would have assumed that paying top dollar for a flat meant
我还以为好歹花了大价钱
that Conrad got someone who is better at reading people
Conrad会找个能察言观色的人呢
Yes.Well,on second thought,I--
好吧 我后来想了想
Which is why I'm loathe to parade around on a goodwill tour with her,
我极度反感和她一起假装友好
not to mention her unresolved feelings for Aiden Mathis
更别提她对Aiden Mathis还余情未了
He's her ex,too
他也是她的前任?
She is determined to make me earn my keep,isn't she
她还真是不让我省心啊
"Too"
"也是"
Well,I probably shouldn't tell you this,
这件事我实在是不该说
but young Emily was married once before
不过Emily曾经结过婚
I beg your pardon
你再说一遍
Don't worry. It was a mistake
别担心 一时失足而已
I'm sure that's all there is to it
我敢保证仅此而已
One can never be too certain
话别说得太满
She was young.She was in love
她那时候还太年轻 又陷入爱河
Did she happen to mention a name
她有说是谁吗
- Oh,I don't remember. - Ronald... Roger
不记得了 Ronald还是Roger
I'm sure I have it at the office
我可以回办公室查一下
Well,perhaps you can do some investigating for me
也许你可以为我做一些调查
And the takedown is all yours,Nolan
下面就交给你了 Nolan
I'm sure the Graysons' 4th of July party will serve
我相信Grayson家的独立日派对
as the perfect backdrop,don't you think
肯定是最好的舞台 你说呢
Well... Let the fireworks begin
好戏上场了
- Nice to see you.- Take care.- Hey,Mom.- Quick photo
- 很高兴见到你 - 保重 - 妈妈 - 来一张吗
Yeah.Okay. Well,Bizzy's certainly making this an event to remember
Bizzy确实想让这个派对变得难忘
She's documenting every living inch of it
她可是记录了点点滴滴啊
Well,I'm sure she'll be excluding Aiden,
我估计她会略去Aiden的
seeing as he dragged your fiancée out of lunch today
今天午餐时 他把你的未婚妻叫走了
Emily told you,I'm sure
我想Emily肯定和你讲了
I think he's trying to rekindle the relationship
我觉得他肯定想旧情复燃
Do you have to read into everything
你就非得事事钻牛角尖吗
Just try and enjoy yourself
好好享受吧
- Hello,gentlemen. - Hi
- 你们好啊 - 你好啊
The who's who of the Hamptons is out in full force
汉普顿的重量级人物可都到场了
I'd say we're a success
我们成功了
Oh,and I have feelers out for info on husband number one
我已经派人去调查那位前夫了
Speaking of which,I should probably find mine
说到这 我得去找我先生了
Why don't we keep our little fact finding mission to ourselves,shall we
这件事就你知我知怎么样
Mother... You remember Sara
妈妈 你还记得Sara吗
Of course
当然了
Oh,Ms Munello,I don't mean to be indelicate,
Munello小姐 我不想太失礼
but wouldn't you be far more comfortable
不过你在外面随便哪里看看烟花
watching the fireworks in the field somewhere
不是更好吗
Well,Charlotte was nice enough to let me class it up tonight--
Charlotte请我来看看开开眼界
Pretend to be the one percent
来充充数
Of what exactly,dear
充谁的数呢 亲爱的
Can I get you a refill
要给你拿些喝的吗
'Cause I could sure use a drink
我很想来一杯
Why on earth did you invite that girl back into our house
你为什么把那个女孩带家里来
Because I care about Daniel too much to see him marry the wrong woman
因为我关心Daniel的幸福 不想让他娶错人
And I don't think Emily's the one to make him happy
我觉得Emily不是他的真命天女
You know I concur in spades,but that doesn't explain
你知道我再赞同不过了
the need to trot in somebody off the rack
但也不用随随便便就拉个人来啊
Wake up,Mother
醒醒吧 妈妈
I'm sure Daniel still has feelings for Sara, and she still has feelings for him
我肯定Daniel对她还余情未了 她也一样
They just need help remembering that
他们只是还需要点催化剂
So you think that Sara could be the one who would put a stop to this wedding
所以你觉得Sara可以阻止这场婚礼
Well,if you weren't so focused on hating Emily
要是你不那么针对Emily
and were more focused on worrying about Daniel, you might see it,too
而是多关心Daniel 你早就看出来了
So okay... proud of me.I'd expect nothing less
- 怎么样 为我骄傲不 - 向来如此
Bizzy Preston... In the flesh
这不是Bizzy Preston吗
Nols.It's been ages
Nols 好久不见了
Darling,you look marvelous
亲爱的 你看起来棒极了
Likewise,and,uh,who's the arm candy
彼此彼此 这位俊男是
This is my husband Jeff
这是我先生 Jeff
Jeff,this is Nolan Ross
Jeff 这是Nolan Ross
of course.Pleasure to meet you,Nolan
当然了 很高兴见到你 Nolan
Oh,the pleasure is all mine
我也是
You dabble in PR as well?
你也是搞公关的?
Oh,no,no. I let my wife stay in the spotlight
不是 我不抢妻子的风头
She's good at it
她真的很擅长
She is dedicated to her clients
她对客户可是敬忠职守啊
You know,come to think of it,the last time we crossed paths,
说到这我想起来了 上次我们接触的时候
you were a bad girl,outing me like that in the press
你可真不乖呢 告诉媒体我的性取向
You mean that whole "Sage" thing
你是说"Sage"那件事
You're welcome
不用谢
I took you out of the tech pages, and I made you interesting to real people
我让你在科技领域外出了名 引起了大众的兴趣
You did bring out my inner Armani
你确实带出了我的真性情
And besides,who could stay mad at that face
再说了 谁能对这样的脸庞生气呢
You just earned a cocktail
我得奖励你杯鸡尾酒
I wore this for one night as a married man,
这枚婚戒 作为丈夫 我只戴了一夜
and I've worn it ever since to honor you...
此后的日子 我戴着只为纪念你
Maybe subconsciously to convince people
也许是潜意识里想让人相信
that I had someone to share my days with,and... And nights
这些日夜 我也是有人相伴的
But I don't anymore
但我已无人相伴了
It's time for me to try to move on
是时候向前看了
I miss you with all my heart
我真的好想你
I'm serious .The orange jumpsuit washed me out
说真的 橙色连体衣太不称我
So I said I preferred the black and white stripes
所以我说 我还是要黑白条的吧
They wouldn't budge
他们就是不肯
You are too much
你太逗了
You two seem to be having a good time
你们看起来处得不错啊
Oh,Emily,you are so lucky to have this one at arm's length
Emily 有他在身边 你太幸运了
God,the trouble you two must get into
你俩肯定没少闯祸吧
Nothing worth publicizing
没什么好宣传的
I was gonna ask you,
我想问你
what time is that museum fund-raiser on Monday
星期一的博物馆募捐是什么时候来着
Victoria would kill me if I'm late
要是迟到了 Victoria不会放过我的
- As will I? - Let me check
我也不会 让我看看
Where are my readers
我的眼镜呢
Oh,here,these, These are mine
给你 用我的好了
Oh,thank you,Nols.My little lifesaver
谢谢 Nols 你是我的救星啊
10:00
10点
And it is very important that you two put on - a good show,my dear
你们两个一定要好好表现啊
I will behave,I promise
我保证会的
- Enjoy the party . - Thank you
- 好好玩 - 谢谢
Now,where were we
我们说到哪里了
Well,I was just about to get,uh,another cocktail
我想再去拿杯鸡尾酒
What's your poison
你要什么
Surprise me
给我个惊喜吧
- Okay. - Oh,hi
- 好的 - 你好啊
Thank you,Nols,my little lifesaver
谢谢 Nols 你是我的救星啊
If it's a surprise you want, I'm more than happy to oblige
想要惊喜 我可是乐意效劳啊
You're looking dashing this evening,Ms Thorne
你今晚真是光彩照人 Thorne小姐
As are you,MrMathis
你也是 Mathis先生
Well,I see you two have made peace
看来你们能和平共处了啊
We're trying,Victoria,seeing as you obviously intend on having us both in your life
努力中 Victoria 显然你执意要把我俩都留在身边
Oh,aren't you kind
你太贴心了
But don't do anything on my behalf
但无需拿我当借口
Well,that wasn't part of the plan
这可不在计划之中
Victoria forced my hand
Victoria逼我的
I had no choice but to be seen with you
大家必须看到我们在一起
Mm,don't get used to it
别太习惯就好
Getting chummy with Aiden again
和Aiden和好了啊
Oh,we're just at the same party,Daniel
只不过在派对碰到而已 Daniel
What did he have to say
他说什么了
Does it matter
无关紧要了
I'm just making the best of a bad situation
我也只是避免弄得太尴尬而已
Don't tell me you're jealous
你不会吃醋了吧
-No No,I'm not - Good
- 当然没有了 - 那就好
I was gonna go get some food,if you want to join
我准备去吃点东西 一起吗
- In a minute I got a couple people I need to talk to. -Okay
- 一会就去 还要和几个人谈谈 - 好的
Word around the party is that Conrad Grayson is writing his memoirs
据说Conrad Grayson要出回忆录了啊
Is this true
是真的吗
Indeed it is.Will you excuse us
千真万确 失陪一下
So you've decided to discuss your past after all
所以你最终打算回忆过去了
Well,you were right
是啊 你说得对
The public deserves it
公众有权知道我的过去
I plan to give it to them in my own way
我打算以我的方式陈述事实
Well,I would love to talk more about it
那我想和你详谈此事
Perhaps tomorrow morning at my office
明早在我办公室怎么样
I'm afraid that ship has sailed
你已经错过机会了
I don't want mere excerpts for Voulez,MrGrayson
我可不是要在Voulez上登登书摘 Grayson先生
- No - I want your whole book
- 不是吗 - 我想要整本书
Have you forgotten Lemarchal has a publishing arm
难道你忘了吗 Lemarchal还有个出版部门
- Well,then tomorrow morning it is. - Okay
- 那明天早上见 - 好的
Hey. Look,I'm sorry about the other night
那晚的事我很抱歉
- It's been a rough year
这一年我过的很艰难
- I can't imagine
我无法想象
Look,I haven't brought it up because I felt you didn't wanna talk about it
我没有提起这事 是因为我以为你不想谈
I didn't
我确实不想谈
That's... part of the problem
这 也是问题之一
But... I hope that you'll give me another chance
但 我希望你能再给我一次机会
You took off your ring
你把戒指摘了
What do you say we go watch the fireworks on your roof
我们去你家屋顶看烟火怎么样
Hey.I brought you a jacket
我给你带了件外套
Hope you're not hiding from my mother
你不会是在躲着我母亲吧
She doesn't scare me anymore
我已经不怕她了
But,man,does she still try
但是 她还是不肯罢休
Yeah,she tends to go all out. - Clearly
- 是啊 她总是全力以赴 - 可不是吗
Yeah,I wouldn't miss this show
我不会错过表演的
I remember my mom taking us kids out every weekend
我还记得小时候 在这个季节 每个周末
during the season to see them on Coney Island
妈妈都会带我们 去科尼岛上看烟火
Yeah,Friday nights on the boardwalk.9:30 sharp
是啊 周五晚 在木板路上 九点半准时开始
Oh,you've been
你也去过?
Best seats in the house are between 10th and 15th
最好的座位在10排和15排之间
- Never missed it as a kid. - No way
- 小时候从来不会错过 - 不会吧
Of course,I was with my nanny,but... Who knows
当然我是和保姆在一起 但 谁知道呢
Maybe we met once at the hot dog stand
也许我们曾经在热狗摊擦肩而过
If you had told me I'd ever be back here sitting next to you
真不敢相信我还会回到这 坐在你身边
- Well... Things change . - Yeah
- 世事无常 - 是啊
Guess you're right
我想你是对的
You're hacking Bizzy's phone here
你就在这儿黑进Bizzy的手机吗
What if somebody saw you
有人看见你怎么办
What? I got excited
我太激动了
Plus I waited till she left
而且我是等到她离开才开始的
Did you get what you needed
找到你需要的信息了吗
And so much more
不止如此
Check out this string of dirty texts from Ms Preston herself
看看Preston女士自己发的 这些下流的短信
Wait Trevor
等等 Trevor
- I thought her husband's name was Jeff. - It is.
- 我以为她丈夫叫Jeff - 是的
Seems our dear Bizzy has been getting busy covering up stories of her own
看来我们亲爱的Bizzy一直忙于 掩盖自己的秘密呢
Drink
来一杯?
I don't want us to rush anything
我们不必太着急的
We can go up and watch the fireworks
我们可以先去上面看烟花
What's this
这是干吗
It's the 4th of July, the day we Americans celebrate ridding ourselves of the British
今天是七月四日 这一天我们美国 人民要庆祝摆脱英国的统治
But I'm making progress
但我已经有进展了
I have Emily in good graces
我得到了Emily的青睐
Well,your sad attempts at wooing her have failed to have their desired effect
可是 这样努力追求她 也没达到预期的效果
Daniel's unconcerned with your renewed relationship
Daniel对你们的关系毫不在意
Well,then I'll change his mind
那我就改变他的想法
Oh,but you don't seem to understand
你好像还没听懂
I'm declaring my independence
我宣告独立
Victoria,you can't deny that we've made a good team thus far,
Victoria 你无法否认 到目前为止 我们一直合作得很愉快
and... besides... You can't do this alone
而且 你一个人可做不来
Oh,you underestimate me,Mr Mathis
你太低估我了 Mathis先生
Yet another reason why your time here is over
这更让我确定必须让你离开
So if you don't mind... Get the hell out of my house
如果你不介意的话 滚出我的房子
- What happened? - I don't know .Victoria's gone crazy
- 出什么事了 - 我也不知道Victoria发了什么疯
She just kicked me out on a whim
突然心血来潮把我赶走了
Means she's got something else up her sleeve
这说明她有别的花招了
And I'll be damned if I don't find out what it is
我不查出来决不罢休
Just don't overreact
别反应过激了
I don't want her to get suspicious
我不想让她起疑
Well,then what can I do to help
那有何需要我帮忙
Just go make sure everything's ready for when this is done
只要确保事成之后 一切都准备就绪
Come back when the dust settles
尘埃落定以后再回来吧
Well,at least I get to say good-bye this time
至少这次可以跟你说再见了
Here you go
给你
If you want something fancier,I can run downstairs
如果你想要更上档次的 我可以下楼去弄
Oh,do you have an espresso machine
你有咖啡机?
No,no,I just meant I can put it in a nicer mug
没有 我的意思是 我可以换个更好的杯子
Okay
好吧
Oh,I'm afraid I need to get to the office
恐怕我得去工作了
Stay for breakfast
吃完早饭再走吧
I make a mean pancake
我做的煎饼很赞
Rain check,please
下次吧
No,I'm hearing a book proposal this morning,
我今天早上要谈一个出版计划
and I imagine Conrad Grayson waits for no one
我想Conrad Grayson不喜欢等人
- Conrad .- Mm-hmm
- Conrad? - 对的
What's he pitching,a book of lies
他有什么可写的 满纸谎言吗
Probably,but that doesn't mean I can't get the real story
很可能 但那不意味着我挖不出真相
I have a feeling it's much more interesting than any of us know
我有预感 这会比我们 已经知道的更有趣
- Hi - Great party last night
嗨 昨晚的聚会很棒吧
Can you believe the Graysons are trending
你能相信Grayson家已经上话题榜了
Oh,I can
我相信
You do anything for your clients,don't you
你愿意为客户做任何事 是吗
Even if it hurts someone else
哪怕伤及无辜
Are you still on about that story I planted in the press years ago
你还在记恨多年前 我漏给媒体的那条新闻吗
Oh You mean the one that nearly destroyed me
你是说那个几乎毁掉我的故事吗
That left me feeling completely alone,
那个让我感到无比孤独
that cost me the last ten years of my father's life
害我在父亲生前最后十年 都不能和他见面的故事吗
Yeah You did that
对 正是你所为
So why are you here
那你为什么来这
For payback
报复
Well... See,at first, I was just going to out all of your clients' secrets,
起初 我只是想公开 你所有客户的秘密
but then I thought,well,it's not their fault
但我转念一想 这不是他们的错
they have drug and anger issues
他们有吸毒和暴力的问题
Oh,and that,guy with the thing for the diapers...
还有喜欢尿布的那位仁兄
How do you know about that
你是怎么知道的
That is totally secure information
那都是安全信息
Little birdie told me
小鸟告诉我的
And then... Sent e-mails to all your clients,
然后给所有客户发封邮件
explaining how sloppy you are at guarding their sins
解释你是多么粗心 没有保护好他们罪恶的秘密
You'll destroy my career
你想毁了我的事业
Ah,well,Bizzy,I already did
那个 Bizzy 我已经毁了
And... Now that you're officially out of business, you're mine
现在你正式失业了 你得听我的
Now if and when I need you,I'll call
从现在开始 如果我需要你 我会给你打电话
Otherwise,that phone stays silent
除此之外 不许用手机
And that includes sexting Trevor Vance
也不能给Trevor Vance发色情短信
I don't know who that is
我不知道他是谁
Then why do you visit his house in Westport three nights a week
那你为什么每周有三个晚上 都要去他在Westport的家呢
Nolan... Jeff's... He's a good man
Nolan Jeff他是个好人
And it would kill him if he found out
如果他知道了 会很痛苦的
All right
好吧
Then I'll give you a choice--
那我给你个选择
One that you never had the courtesy to extend to me all of those years ago
多年前你却没给我留这个余地
End the affair... Today
你这段外遇 今天就结束
Go back to the man that clearly loves you
回到那个真正爱你的人身边
Otherwise... I tell him the truth
否则 我就告诉他实情
I am sorry... About what happened with your father
你父亲的事情 我很抱歉
I've waited ten years to hear that
这句话我等了十年
It's just too bad he never will
可惜他永远听不到了
I wanted to apologize for my coldness toward you last night
昨晚对你那么冷淡 我很抱歉
It's a long way to hike for two words you can say on the phone
一句话 你在电话里说就行了 何必大老远来这
Well,then would you indulge me for a few more
那么 允许我多说几句
I know that Daniel once fancied you
我知道Daniel曾经很喜欢你
and that I wasn't the most receptive to your presence
可是我不太能接受你
You think
是吗
That's because I didn't fully understand
那是因为我当时没有完全理解
how important his happiness was to me... Exclusive of my own
他的幸福对我来讲有多重要 无论我自己幸福与否
What are you saying
你想说什么
That I think that you may be the one for Daniel
我觉得你更适合Daniel
Daniel's getting married in a month
Daniel还有一个月就要结婚了
But you must have stopped to wonder if
但你一定想过
that was only because he lost you three years ago
这只是因为他三年前失去你了
I know that you and I didn't get along in the past,
我知道我们过去相处得不好
but perhaps we could work together towards a common goal
但也许我们可以向着 共同的目标携手合作
My museum fund-raiser's canceled
我的博物馆募捐会被取消了
I imagine I have you to thank for that
我想这得感谢你吧
- Bizzy will be anything but for a while - Thanks
- Bizzy暂时搞不出什么名堂了 - 谢谢
Though when it was time to go in for the kill,
可是真到了该收拾她的时候
I couldn't pull the trigger
我却下不了手
I actually saved her marriage
我还挽救了她的婚姻
Guess my takedowns have a silver lining,
看来我的报复还带着一线曙光
It's kind of fun being your wingman
当你的助手还挺有意思的
I taught you well,grasshopper
那是我教的好
You know,actually,you did,Nolan
确实是 Nolan
Two years ago,I never would've thought
两年前 我决不会想到
I'd have a partner in all this... Or a real friend
我会有个搭档 或者说 一个真正的朋友
Well,you, Might wanna wait on our freeze-frame high five
你可能不要高兴得太早
My glasses accidentally pocket-recorded portions of last night's party
我的眼镜意外记录了 昨晚聚会的一些场景
Allow me to jump to the lowlight
我直接跳到低潮吧 看
Wait for it... That's why Daniel wasn't upset about Aiden
这就是Daniel没因Aiden生气的原因
Looks like they're about to rekindle their past
看起来他们要重燃旧爱了
Then I have to make sure they have no future
那我必须确保他们没有未来
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-Proudly Presents
-=伊甸园美剧  http://bbs.sfile2012.com=- -=伊甸园字幕站   http://ytet.org=- 荣誉出品 本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com/bbs=-Sync: YTET-可可与可心
-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组=- 翻译:becausel 可可 豆芽小鱼 藉秋风 小V 校对:Music4d 时间轴:YTET-可可与可心
Revenge Season3Episode 7
复仇 第三季 第七集 完